<parameters>
<query id="501">What is the difference between deduction and induction in the process of reasoning?  </query>
<query id="502">What is a prime factor?  </query>
<query id="503">What hard evidence proves that the Vikings visited or lived in Scotland?  </query>
<query id="504">Find documents that describe the diet of the manatee.  </query>
<query id="505">Who is/was Edmund Hillary?  </query>
<query id="506">What is the history of skateboarding?  </query>
<query id="507">Find documents that report on the recall of any Dodge automobile products.  </query>
<query id="508">Find diseases for which hair loss is a symptom.  </query>
<query id="509">What effect do steroids have on the human body?  </query>
<query id="510">Find biographical data on J. Robert Oppenheimer.  </query>
<query id="511">What diseases does smoking cause?  </query>
<query id="512">How are tornadoes formed?  </query>
<query id="513">What causes earthquakes, and where do they occur most often?  </query>
<query id="514">Find documents that discuss the financial aspects of retirement planning.  </query>
<query id="515">What did Alexander Graham Bell invent?  </query>
<query id="516">When, where, and how did Halloween evolve?    </query>
<query id="517">Find documents that discuss the reasons for or problems leading to the sinking of the Titanic.  </query>
<query id="518">Find documents that reference the use of statistical data in decision-making.  </query>
<query id="519">Find documents that describe the habitat of frogs.  </query>
<query id="520">What measures were taken to end the black plague?  </query>
<query id="521">Identify the best places to live as judged by various surveys and magazines.  </query>
<query id="522">Identify methods being used to provide water to the Mojave Desert region   </query>
<query id="523">How are the five main types of clouds formed?  </query>
<query id="524">What methods are used for removal of scar tissue?  </query>
<query id="525">How does water enter the earth's atmosphere?  </query>
<query id="526">What does BMI stand for?  </query>
<query id="527">What biographical data is available on Booker T. Washington?  </query>
<query id="528">How does a hygrometer measure the humidity in the atmosphere?  </query>
<query id="529">Find accounts of the history of Cambodia.  </query>
<query id="530">What is the scientific evidence that suggests pheromones stimulate the opposite sex?  </query>
<query id="531">What is the proper grammatical use of "who" versus "whom"?.  </query>
<query id="532">Find documents that describe the uses of hypnosis, and report on how effective hypnosis is.  </query>
<query id="533">Find documents either pro or con regarding children wearing uniforms in public schools.  </query>
<query id="534">Find items referencing artists who died in the 1700's.  </query>
<query id="535">Find documents describing Canadian building codes.  </query>
<query id="536">Would eating honey affect the health of a baby?  </query>
<query id="537">Are sun beds detrimental to the health of an individual?  </query>
<query id="538">Find documents describing the Federal Housing Administration (FHA): when and why it was originally established and its current mission.  </query>
<query id="539">Which authors suffered from depression?  </query>
<query id="540">Find descriptions of studies that correlate stress and obesity.  </query>
<query id="541">What instruments are used to forecast the weather?  </query>
<query id="542">What are the positive effects of forest fires?  </query>
<query id="543">What are the hazards associated with radiography?  </query>
<query id="544">Find documents that describe the roles estrogen plays in the human body.  </query>
<query id="545">What did Peter the Great accomplish for Russia?  </query>
<query id="546">What are the benefits of recycling cans?  </query>
<query id="547">Why were camels domesticated?  </query>
<query id="548">What are the methods of using solar heat to warm up the water in a swimming pool?  </query>
<query id="549">Find documents that contrast cancer with normal cell reproduction.  </query>
<query id="550">Find documents that describe how volcanoes are formed.  </query>
</parameters>
