<parameters>
<query id="26">  How can I lower my heart rate? </query>
<query id="27">  Find information about the coffee company Starbucks. </query>
<query id="28">  Find information about InuYasha, the Japanese comic book and animated cartoon franchise.   </query>
<query id="29">  Find information, reviews, and cheat codes for Playstation 2 games.   </query>
<query id="30">  I'm looking for online resources to learn and teach others about diabetes.   </query>
<query id="31">  Find information about Atari, its game consoles and games. </query>
<query id="32">  I'm looking for information on designing a business website and finding hosting for it.   </query>
<query id="33">  Find information about elliptical trainer machines. </query>
<query id="34">  Find information about cell phones and cellular service providers.   </query>
<query id="35">  Find information on the city of Hoboken, New Jersey.</query>
<query id="36">  I'm looking for information about and comparisons of  GPS receivers.   </query>
<query id="37">  Find out about hosting a cooking show from The Pampered Chef </query>
<query id="38">  I want to adopt a dog.  Where can I do that and what  should I know?   </query>
<query id="39">  Find information about hotels near Disneyland in  Anaheim, California.   </query>
<query id="40">  Find information on getting a job in Michigan. </query>
<query id="41">  Looking for information about the Orange County  Convention Center in Orlando, Florida.   </query>
<query id="42">  Find songs, lyrics, music, and information about the  musical The Music Man   </query>
<query id="43">  Find information and reviews about The Secret Garden  book by Frances Hodgson Burnett, as well as movies and the musical   based on it.   </query>
<query id="44">  Find maps of the United States. </query>
<query id="45">  Find information about solar panels and companies that  manufacture them.   </query>
<query id="46">  Find information about the Alexian Brothers and  hospitals they run.   </query>
<query id="47">  I'm looking for information about indexed annuities.</query>
<query id="48">  Find information about Wilson CB antennas. </query>
<query id="49">  I am looking for flame graphics to use on a website.</query>
<query id="50">  What is the effect of excessive heat on dogs?</query>
</parameters>
