<parameters>
<query id="100">how to "open up" a cell through a process called "electroporation."</query>
<query id="101">exact reactions that take place when you do glutathione S-transferase (GST) cleavage during affinity chromatography.</query>
<query id="102">different quantities of different components to use when pouring a gel to make it more or less porous.</query>
<query id="103">green fluorescent protein (GFP) tagged proteins to do experiments with tagged proteins.</query>
<query id="104">how to do a microsomal budding assay, i.e., budding of vesicles from microsomes in vitro.</query>
<query id="105">purification of rat IgM.</query>
<query id="106">chromatin IP (Immuno Precipitations) to isolate proteins that are bound to DNA in order to precipitate the proteins out of the DNA.</query>
<query id="107">normalization procedures that are used for microarray data.</query>
<query id="108">identifying in vivo protein-protein interactions in time and space in the living cell.</query>
<query id="109">fluorogenic 5'-nuclease assay.</query>
<query id="110">the role of the gene Interferon-beta in the disease Multiple Sclerosis.</query>
<query id="111">the role of the gene PRNP in the disease Mad Cow Disease.</query>
<query id="112">the role of the gene IDE gene in the disease Alzheimer's Disease.</query>
<query id="113">the role of the gene MMS2 in the disease Cancer.</query>
<query id="114">the role of the gene APC (adenomatous polyposis coli) in the disease Colon Cancer.</query>
<query id="115">the role of the gene Nurr-77 in the disease Parkinson's Disease.</query>
<query id="116">the role of the gene Insulin receptor gene in the disease Cancer.</query>
<query id="117">the role of the gene Apolipoprotein E (ApoE) in the disease Alzheimer's Disease.</query>
<query id="118">the role of the gene Transforming growth factor-beta1 (TGF-beta1) in the disease Cerebral Amyloid Angiopathy (CAA).</query>
<query id="119">the role of the gene GSTM1 in the disease Breast Cancer.</query>
<query id="120">the role of the gene nucleoside diphosphate kinase  (NM23) in the process of tumor progression.</query>
<query id="121">the role of the gene BARD1 in the process of BRCA1 regulation.</query>
<query id="122">the role of the gene APC (adenomatous polyposis coli) in the process of actin assembly.</query>
<query id="123">the role of the gene COP2 in the process of transport of CFTR out of the endoplasmic reticulum.</query>
<query id="124">the role of the gene casein kinase II in the process of ribosome assembly.</query>
<query id="125">the role of the gene Nurr-77 in the process of preventing auto-immunity by deleting reactive T-cells  before they migrate to the spleen or the lymph nodes.</query>
<query id="126">the role of the gene P53 in the process of apoptosis.</query>
<query id="127">the role of the gene alpha7 nicotinic receptor subunit gene in the process of ethanol metabolism.</query>
<query id="128">the role of the gene gamma-aminobutyric acid receptors (GABABRs) in the process of inhibitory synaptic transmission.</query>
<query id="129">the role of the gene Interferon-beta in the process of viral entry into host cell.</query>
<query id="130">the genes BRCA1 regulation of ubiquitin in cancer.</query>
<query id="131">the genes L1 and L2 in the HPV11 virus in the role of L2 in the viral capsid.</query>
<query id="132">the genes APC (adenomatous polyposis coli) and wnt in colon cancer.</query>
<query id="133">the genes phospholipase A2 (PLA2) and SAR1 in Endoplasmic reticulum transport (i.e. vesicle budding from the ER).</query>
<query id="134">the genes CFTR and Sec61 in degradation of CFTRwhich leads to cystic fibrosis.</query>
<query id="135">the genes Bop and Pes in cell growth.</query>
<query id="136">the genes alpha7 nicotinic receptor gene and ApoE gene in the neurotoxic effects of ethanol.</query>
<query id="137">the genes Insulin-like GF and insulin receptor gene in the function in skin.</query>
<query id="138">the genes HNF4 and COUP-TF I in the suppression in the function of the liver.</query>
<query id="139">the genes Ret and GDNF in kidney development.</query>
<query id="140">BRCA1 185delAG mutation and its/their role in ovarian cancer.</query>
<query id="141">Huntingtin mutations and its/their role in Huntington's Disease.</query>
<query id="142">Sonic hedgehog mutations and its/their role in developmental disorders.</query>
<query id="143">Mutations of NM23 and its/their impact on tracheal development.</query>
<query id="144">Mutations in metazoan Pes and its/their effect on cell growth.</query>
<query id="145">Mutations of hypocretin receptor 2 and its/their role in narcolepsy.</query>
<query id="146">Mutations of presenilin-1 gene and its/their biological impact in Alzheimer's disease.</query>
<query id="147">Mutations of alpha7 nAChR gene and its/their biological impact in alcoholism.</query>
<query id="148">Mutation of familial hemiplegic migraine type 1 (FHM1) and its/their neuronal Ca2+ influx in hippocampal neurons.</query>
<query id="149">Mutations of the alpha 4-GABAA receptor and its/their impact on behavior.</query>
</parameters>
