<parameters>
<query id="2">what is the relationship between the movi " ride alon for thousand of mile " and zhang yimou ?;What is the relationship between the movie "Riding Alone for Thousands of Miles" and ZHANG Yimou?</query>
<query id="5">what is the definit of age societi ?;What is the definition of Aging Society?</query>
<query id="6">what is the relationship between bali bomb and bin laden ?;What is the relationship between Bali bombings and Bin Laden?</query>
<query id="9">where will olymp game 2008 be held ?;Where will Olympics Game 2008 be held?</query>
<query id="12">what is the virus of sar ?;What is the virus of SARS?</query>
<query id="15">where will expo 2010 be held ?;Where will Expo 2010 be held?</query>
<query id="16">whi doe china want to import technolog to build shanghai maglev railway ?;Why does China want to import technology to build Shanghai Maglev Railway?</query>
<query id="18">what is the six - parti talk ?;What is the Six-Party Talks?</query>
<query id="19">what is the definit of obes ?;What is the definition of obesity?</query>
<query id="23">whi doe the bird flu threat to human ?;Why does the bird flu threat to humans?</query>
<query id="26">what is the relationship between liu guoliang and the men 's tabl tenni team of china ?;What is the relationship between Liu Guoliang and the men's table tennis team of China?</query>
<query id="28">which organ declar nobel prize in literatur ?;Which organization declares Nobel Prize in Literature?</query>
<query id="29">what is the relationship of yong - bo li and the chines badminton team ?;What is the relationship of Yong-Bo Li and the Chinese badminton team?</query>
<query id="30">impress seri of zhang yimou .;impression series of Zhang Yimou.</query>
<query id="32">what is the relationship between liu xiang and johnson ?;What is the relationship between Liu Xiang and Johnson?</query>
<query id="33">event relat to the taliban and the unit state;events related to the Taliban and the United States</query>
<query id="35">event relat to the movi " initi d " .;events related to the movie "Initials D".</query>
<query id="36">movi in which zhao wei particip .;movies in which Zhao Wei participated.</query>
<query id="38">what is the relationship between xia yu and yuan quan ?;What is the relationship between Xia Yu and Yuan Quan?</query>
<query id="39">new year film made by feng xiaogang .;new year films made by Feng Xiaogang.</query>
<query id="40">what is the relationship between guo jingj and wu minxia ?;What is the relationship between Guo Jingjing and Wu Minxia?</query>
<query id="41">who is the 2004 us presidenti democrat candid ?;Who is the 2004 US Presidential Democratic candidate?</query>
<query id="42">what is the interrelationship between the petroleum industri and war ?;What is the interrelationship between the petroleum industry and wars?</query>
<query id="43">what econom impact might olymp game have on host countri ?;What economic impact might Olympic Games have on host countries?</query>
<query id="44">how ultraviolet light might threaten human health ?;How ultraviolet light might threaten human health?</query>
<query id="45">when did arafat pass away ?;When did Arafat pass away?</query>
<query id="46">which year was macau 's return to china ?;Which year was Macau's return to China?</query>
<query id="47">who is david ho( da - i ho ) ?;Who is David Ho(Da-i Ho)?</query>
<query id="48">who is sean chen( chen shin - an ) ?;Who is Sean Chen(Chen Shin-An)?</query>
<query id="49">who is lung yingtai ?;Who is Lung Yingtai?</query>
<query id="51">what doe " dink " repres ?;What does "DINK" represent?</query>
<query id="52">what is cholesterol ?;What is cholesterol?</query>
<query id="53">what is " thangka " ?;What is "Thangka"?</query>
<query id="54">what happen on the day of 7 juli 2005 london underground bomb ?;What happened on the day of 7 July 2005 London Underground bombings?</query>
<query id="56">what is the disput about china - russia eastern border agreement ?;what is the disputes about China-Russia eastern border agreement?</query>
<query id="57">what is the disput between china and japan for the undersea natur gas field in the east china sea ?;What is the disputes between China and Japan for the undersea natural gas field in the East China Sea?</query>
<query id="58">whi did the box day tsunami caus serious damag and death along the coast of indonesia , sri lanka , india , and thailand ?;Why did the Boxing Day Tsunami cause serious damage and deaths along the coasts of Indonesia, Sri Lanka, India, and Thailand?</query>
<query id="59">what is the reason that 2003 invas of iraq was led by the us ?;What is the reason that 2003 invasion of Iraq was led by the US?</query>
<query id="61">which compani is terri guo ( tai - ming guo ) presid of ?;Which company is Terry Guo (Tai-Ming Guo) president of?</query>
<query id="62">who was the presid of the unit state when cheney serv as vice presid ?;Who was the President of the United States when Cheney served as Vice President?</query>
<query id="63">who serv as the head of the plo negoti affair depart , and minist of negoti in prime minist qureia 's first cabinet ?;Who served as the Head of the PLO Negotiation Affairs Department, and Minister of Negotiations in Prime Minister Qureia's first cabinet?</query>
<query id="64">how was al - zarqawi involv in the japanes hostag incid in iraq ?;How was al-Zarqawi involved in the Japanese hostage incident in Iraq?</query>
<query id="65">describ the relationship between brazil and china , which have joint launch an earth resourc satellit .;Describe the relationship between Brazil and China, which have jointly launched an earth resources satellite.</query>
<query id="66">what is the relationship between two russian politician , kasianov and putin ?;What is the relationship between two Russian politicians, Kasianov and Putin?</query>
<query id="67">what is the relationship between the uk and the euro ?;What is the relationship between the UK and the euro?</query>
<query id="68">when was the kyoto protocol enforc ?;When was the Kyoto Protocol enforced?</query>
<query id="69">who is masatoshi koshiba ?;Who is Masatoshi Koshiba?</query>
<query id="70">who is koichi tanaka ?;Who is Koichi Tanaka?</query>
<query id="71">who is chen shui - bian ?;Who is Chen Shui-Bian?</query>
<query id="72">what are embryon stem cell ?;What are embryonic stem cells?</query>
<query id="73">what is hansen 's diseas ?;What is Hansen's disease?</query>
<query id="74">where are japan 's northern territori locat ?;Where are Japan's Northern Territories located?</query>
<query id="75">which countri have border in the kashimir region ?;Which countries have borders in the Kashimir region?</query>
<query id="76">where is the gaza strip locat ?;Where is the Gaza Strip located?</query>
<query id="77">what was the bse incid ?;What was the BSE incident?</query>
<query id="78">what are the characterist of the largest earthquak that occur off the coast of sumatra , indonesia ?;What are the characteristics of the largest earthquake that occurred off the coast of Sumatra, Indonesia?</query>
<query id="80">describ the iraq war , which start in march 2003 and was fought between regular militari forc .;Describe the Iraq War, which started in March 2003 and was fought between regular military forces.</query>
<query id="82">whi did japan 's dispatch of the self - defens forc to iraq trigger a debat over amend of the japanes constitut ?;Why did Japan's dispatch of the Self-Defense Force to Iraq trigger a debate over amendment of the Japanese Constitution?</query>
<query id="83">whi did the argentin econom crisi occur ?;Why did the Argentine economic crisis occur?</query>
<query id="84">whi did franc vote against the eu constitut ?;Why did France vote against the EU Constitution?</query>
<query id="85">whi did oil price rise sharpli in 2004 ?;Why did oil prices rise sharply in 2004?</query>
<query id="87">what is the relationship between sleep and health ?;What is the relationship between sleep and health?</query>
<query id="90">what is the relationship between the strait of malacca and the japanes peopl ?;What is the relationship between the Straits of Malacca and the Japanese people?</query>
<query id="91">what link are there between japan and the reconstruct of iraq ?;What links are there between Japan and the reconstruction of Iraq?</query>
<query id="92">what is the import issu of the negoti between india and pakistan ?;What is the important issues of the Negotiation between India and Pakistan?</query>
<query id="93">what is the contribut of three gorg dam ?;What is the contributions of Three Gorges Dam?</query>
<query id="94">could you pleas give short descript to the salt lake winter olymp game of 2002 ?;Could you please give short descriptions to the Salt Lake Winter Olympic Games of 2002?</query>
<query id="95">whi had sar report expand rapid from 2003 ?;Why had SARS reports expanded rapidly from 2003?</query>
<query id="96">whi is iraq war a polit tip point to presid bush ?;Why is Iraq War a political tipping point to President Bush?</query>
<query id="97">whi did china make a bid to host the 2008 summer olymp ?;Why did China make a bid to host the 2008 Summer Olympics?</query>
<query id="98">whi did arm chechen hold eight hundr hostag in moscow theater in 2002 ?;Why did armed Chechens hold eight hundred hostages in Moscow theater in 2002?</query>
<query id="99">whi did china implement the renminbi exchang rate reform in juli 2005 ?;Why did China implement the Renminbi exchange rate reform in July 2005?</query>
<query id="100">whi did u.s. troop occupi baghdad ?;Why did U.S. troops occupy Baghdad?</query>
</parameters>
